如果你的回答是异步任务，那么你是正确的
If you answered A sync Task, then you are correct.
为了弄清为什么我们选择异步任务作为答案
To understand why we chose Async Task as the answer,
我们可以查阅一下开发者文档
we can check the developer documentation. In this API
在API指南的进程与线程部分，滚动到
guide on processes and threads, we can scroll to the
worker threads这一段。如果你想现在
Worker threads section. Right away, if you want to follow
就去查阅，链接就在底部了。
along, the link is included below. Say, for example, that
比如，你想从网络上
you want to download an image from the network
下载一张图片然后更新UI
at this URL and then you want to update the
来显示这个图片，那好，创建你自己的下载
UI so that it displays this bitmap. Well, creating
图片的线程是有价值的选项
your own thread to download the image is a
但是这样会很多额外的开销
valid option, but there's a lot of overhead to
用来保证你的应用线程安全
handle in making you app actually thread safe. After
下载好图片后，不能直接从后台线程里
you download your image, you cannot directly update the
更新UI。然而，Android有一些
UI from a background thread. However, Android has several
选项，可以从其它线程
options to run code that manipulates the UI to
操作UI线程。在这个例子里
run from other threads. In this example, yet another
另外一个runnable已经被创建
runnable is created to get the bitmap result back onto
这个runnable用来返回图片给主线程,更新ImageView
the main thread to update the image view. This solution
这个解决方案稍微有些麻烦，因为你必须管理两个runnable
is a little cumbersome because you have to manage two
为了抽离这种复杂性
runnables here. To abstract away this complexity we can use
我们可以用异步任务，完成后再丢掉它
an async task and then to kick off the async
例如，一旦按钮被点击了
task. For example, when someone clicks a button, then you
你只需要初始化这个任务，然后调用execute函数
just initialize the task, and then you can call execute
再传入它需要的参数
on it, and then pass in any parameters that are needed.
注意，你正在继承一个异步类
Notice that when you're extending the Async class, there's a
有一些你需要指定的属性
couple of generics that you need to specify. The first is
首先是在doInBackground方法里你需要传入类型
the type that will be passed into the do in
这样，如果你想传入一个图片URL，
background method. So, if you want to pass in this image URL
这个URL在这里是一个指定的字符串
that is specified string here and then in doing background
然后在doInBackground里你将得到一个字符串参数
you'll get a string parameter. The second one is for the
第二个是， 你在任务执行的时候得到它的更新进度的类型
type of object that you'll get when you get progress
在这里我们用不到
updates as a task gets executed. We're not using that here,
所以指定为void就可以了
so it's okay to specify that as void. And the third type is type of results
第三个返回结果类型，我们会在onPostExecute函数里把它返回到主线程中
that we'll be sending back to the main thread through the onPostExecute method